<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>meta on Christopher Nguyen - UX Designer</title>
    <link>https://christopher-nguyen.com/tags/meta/</link>
    <description>Recent content in meta on Christopher Nguyen - UX Designer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 02:27:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://christopher-nguyen.com/tags/meta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VR Hackathon - Vox Augment </title>
      <link>https://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/vox-augmento/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 02:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/vox-augmento/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Winner of best technical achievement at &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;2017 Seattle VR Hackathon&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;. VR is a medium that’s quickly becoming a new creative outlet. We believe it is a way of making music based on natural movements, without relying on existing instrument interfaces. The level of immersion can unlock latent musical abilities in new users, or extend the abilities of existing musicians.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edifecs Redesign Part 2 - Web</title>
      <link>https://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/edifecs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 02:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/edifecs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Main corporate website redesign and rebuild was being worked in on in parallel with internal branding changes. The premise was similar to the internal updates. With continued growth in the industry and general progression of technology, the main corporate website needed to be overhauled to reflect the times.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edifecs Redesign Part 1 - Internal</title>
      <link>https://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/intranet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/intranet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As part of the Edifecs rebrand in 2013, most internal and external systems received updates. Part 1 of this endeavor was to enhance many internal systems, such as the company&amp;rsquo;s SharePoint Intranet. The company felt that with the fact the company was rapidly growing, overall enhancements internally were needed to help employees and solidify the brand.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Designer &amp; Web Developer</title>
      <link>https://christopher-nguyen.com/resume/design-philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopher-nguyen.com/resume/design-philosophy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Continually learning the nature of Human Computer Interactions. I study the field of user interaction and experience. I make informed decisions that lead to graphics and mock-ups which are of high quality. Today I am  skilled designer and web developer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
