<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project on Christopher Nguyen - UX Designer</title>
    <link>http://christopher-nguyen.com/tags/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project on Christopher Nguyen - UX Designer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 02:27:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://christopher-nguyen.com/tags/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Edifecs Redesign Part 2 - Web</title>
      <link>http://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/edifecs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 02:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/edifecs/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Main corporate website redesign and rebuild was being worked in on in parallel with internal branding changes. The premise was similar to the internal updates. With continued growth in the industry and general progression of technology, the main corporate website needed to be overhauled to reflect the times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Rebuilding and redesigning the main corporate site over the course year+. Made the site responsive, performant, and more usability. Traffic and other success metrics have all improved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-solution-original.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-solution-original-thumb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;2010 Solution Page&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
        Original Solution Page
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-solution-final.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-solution-thumb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IntCurrnet Solution Page&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
        Current Solution Page
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;problem:34051db0cb11816e38802f96b3984ab6&#34;&gt;Problem&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the time of development, the site (call it 1.0) was built in 2010, and did not receive any major updates or upgrades until the time of the rebuild. During that time, it was not yet common for B2B enterprise companies to employ what is today is part of standard web development, such as responsive design. The design also lacked focus, often copying common design patterns from competitors which were in themselves not focused. To add to the need for change, the company&amp;rsquo;s headcount ballooned year after year, and making sure the corporate website attracted good talent was a must.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-notes.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Table Notes&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Issues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not Responsive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design cluttered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Messaging stale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many technical issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SEO and SEM problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;solutions-and-goals:34051db0cb11816e38802f96b3984ab6&#34;&gt;Solutions and Goals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Build a new modern site (call it 2.0) with a committed focus on web as a platform to better market, educate, and engage customers. Redoing the site 1.0 was not meant to simply be a simple reskin project or even a slight enhancement, but an overhaul. Site 2.0 had all content, graphics, and code redone from scratch. A large multi-department project formed to complete this 1+ year project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this project important change in mindset needed to be adopted for many stakeholders that core pages were no longer independent of each other. The user&amp;rsquo;s journey on a website is just as much a part of the sales journey as anything else. A whole new approach needed to be adopted. New content and education material needed to be made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Target Users&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table class=&#34;mdl-data-table mdl-js-data-table mdl-shadow--2dp full-table&#34;&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th class=&#34;mdl-data-table__cell--non-numeric&#34;&gt;Persona&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Habits&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td class=&#34;mdl-data-table__cell--non-numeric&#34;&gt;Researcher&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Often the first contact in the sales chain, important in passing information to decision makers. Spends a lot of time reading about solutions. Does not make final say in purchase&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td class=&#34;mdl-data-table__cell--non-numeric&#34;&gt;Directors+&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Normally decision makers. Directors and above are involved near the ends of the sales cycle. Spends a lot of time reading through additional offerings&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td class=&#34;mdl-data-table__cell--non-numeric&#34;&gt;Customer&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Already using the solution. Looks for documentation and trainings on the solutions they are using&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;    
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before any content or code was written, it was made clear that business solution pages were no longer just text on a screen. &amp;lsquo;Glorified whitepapers&amp;rsquo; as product marketer once said to me in describing the 1.0 solution pages. Having solution pages in 2.0 become consumable and bite sized was a proven strategy to use. It was decided that content be written in sections with the concept that it would be plugged into other pages as needed. Resources, such as data sheets and white papers would help breakup sections of written content, given call to action items for users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with many large and long term projects, there&amp;rsquo;s a thousand and one details, and I&amp;rsquo;ll cover my focus of design and development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Design/dev output&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Modern development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Modular based design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytics and marketing automation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reusable content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge center and resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-timelines.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Project timelines&#34; /&gt;
*Content sprints&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;design:34051db0cb11816e38802f96b3984ab6&#34;&gt;Design&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two primary design goals achieved, tell a better more cohesive story on the homepage, and simplify the design templates to more easily produce new pages as needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;homepage:34051db0cb11816e38802f96b3984ab6&#34;&gt;Homepage&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Company homepages are often the first page a new or returning user lands on. 2.0&amp;rsquo;s homepage uses a concept &lt;strong&gt;100%&lt;/strong&gt; sections. It is often difficult deliver a direct message when a large B2B company often offers many solutions. By using the 100% method, only one direct message is used per section. Scrolling slides the user into the next or previous section. Content and messaging don&amp;rsquo;t have to fight one another. There is also added benefit to content creation, as product owners can confidently know what is being presented to the user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-homepage-original.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-homepage-original-thumb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Homepage 2011&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
        Original Homepage
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-homepage-final.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-homepage-final-thumb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;FInal Homepage&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
        Current Homepage
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Animations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of the initiative to design a unique homepage within the healthcare IT space, we employed the use of svg animations and interaction. The step is seemingly bold in an industry where you still have users using IE7, and limitations step in the way of many design ideas. A large part of development time was spent creating fallback methods for things that were more &amp;ldquo;experimental&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p data-height=&#34;266&#34; data-theme-id=&#34;dark&#34; data-slug-hash=&#34;vOmoZo&#34; data-default-tab=&#34;result&#34; data-user=&#34;chris480&#34; data-embed-version=&#34;2&#34; data-preview=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;codepen&#34;&gt;See the Pen &lt;a href=&#34;http://codepen.io/chris480/pen/vOmoZo/&#34;&gt;vOmoZo&lt;/a&gt; by Christopher Nguyen (&lt;a href=&#34;http://codepen.io/chris480&#34;&gt;@chris480&lt;/a&gt;) on &lt;a href=&#34;http://codepen.io&#34;&gt;CodePen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script async src=&#34;//assets.codepen.io/assets/embed/ei.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;solution-and-resources:34051db0cb11816e38802f96b3984ab6&#34;&gt;Solution and Resources&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The product solution pages are the key pages on edifecs.com because of the information they deliver. For companies like edifecs, where sales cycles happen over many months or even years depending on the deals at hand, users often come back to these solution pages for information. Selling products is not as good a strategy as selling solutions, and the pages were designed with that in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content Modules&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By better standardizing page layouts, the product owners and other stakeholders could more easily produce consistent content. Many rules were setup to keep the content limited but meaningful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Word count ranges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stricter body copy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphics and diagram guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although there was flexibility within the design, template breaking requests were disallowed. This also reduced code bloat as unique one-off designs would no longer be implemented. The 1.0 site had numerous custom styles, and scripts per page to accommodate a variety of request.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-whiteboard.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Whiteboarding page layouts&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the solution page designs were done, a modifiable powerpoint and word template was given to those writing content. This way they could &amp;lsquo;build&amp;rsquo; their pages, and then the dev team would quickly stage them for broader review.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 1.0 site listed and showed resources mainly on the resources page. Links to resources were often added into the body copy, however, there was very little to distinguish it from other links.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-resources.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Resource Choices&#34; /&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-resources-access.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Example of resource displayed on a solution page&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 2.0 site revamps the way resources are handled in the site overall. Firstly, a color coded labeling was added to each resource type. Secondly, a &lt;strong&gt;Resource Band&lt;/strong&gt; was added to most solution pages that worked to visually separate sections and clearly show off resources. A dedicated resource page was designed and built to allow users to filter through the 100+ documents and videos that are offered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;trainings:34051db0cb11816e38802f96b3984ab6&#34;&gt;Trainings&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A large new offering within 2.0 is a stronger education section. Solutions like edifecs&amp;rsquo; are like many industry tools, a level of mastery can be achieved through training and practice. Enterprise software purchasers know this, and when vetting solutions look to the complete support cycle offered. Edifecs created a training and certificate program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An entire microsite was designed to allow users to get the training they needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/esite-courses.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sample course list&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;development:34051db0cb11816e38802f96b3984ab6&#34;&gt;Development&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both the front and backend were overhauled during development. Because all the content was being rewritten, very little needed to be ported over to the 2.0 site. Overall there was a development focus on speed, performance, and ease of use. Reducing overhead and shortening the time to commit new code and content were crucial moving forward. &amp;ldquo;You have to be up at 6am to publish a press release&amp;rdquo; a content director said to me early on. Scheduling publications was one of the first things I had setup after I heard this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technology Used&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ExpressionEngine CMS (LAMP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hosted Linux Servers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bootstrap framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marketo tracking and forms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many other frameworks, apis, and tools were used in the development of the current edifecs.com site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frontend&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsive design became part of standard practice with the redesign. All the more interactive elements were chosen with compatibility with existing design pattern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Development set limitations on designs to not use performance heavy modules too often on a single page. Using many best practices to attempt a consistent 60fps and overall fast rendering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the 2.0, there was focus on best practices rather than simply getting out the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Backend&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Complementing the frontend, we built our backend to expedite and automate many previously manual tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1.0, page entries contained content. 2.0 changed this so page entries only reference content modules. By separating all the content into separate entry types, overall control and reusability was easily achieved. This way of structuring the backend in 2.0 allowed for greater permission management, as content creators could work more safely on content chunks rather than the whole page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A slew of new automation came forward as well. Mentioned earlier, previous content owners would have to be up at the hour they needed to make a page or piece of written go live. Something that seems standard in an time where CMS like wordpress has had strong publishing features for years, was simply overlooked in the 1.0 site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blog&lt;/strong&gt; - A wordpress blog with a simple theme was also setup in conjunction with the main corporate site. It is primarily used as a thought leadership publishing platform. It was awarded a best healthcare it blog after the first year. It is mostly self-maintained  by a separate team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;integrations:34051db0cb11816e38802f96b3984ab6&#34;&gt;Integrations&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we moved into 2014, more successful marketing automation was needed. Solutions such as Marketo are heavily used. The front and backend had these integrations in mind when being written. Especially with how taxing performance-wise some analytics, it was important to both support the company&amp;rsquo;s business without degrading the user experience for site visitors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;success:34051db0cb11816e38802f96b3984ab6&#34;&gt;Success&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since launch, the 2.0 site has continued evolve and grow. Traffic has increased while bounce rates have dropped. Leads have been generated, and trainings sold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;completion:34051db0cb11816e38802f96b3984ab6&#34;&gt;Completion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Completing design and development of both the corporate website and internal sites did not mean they were finished. With the new processes created, these web properties continue to receive updates, and new developments which provide more to the users&amp;rsquo; experience almost every day. Hopefully no major overhauls for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edifecs Redesign Part 1 - Internal</title>
      <link>http://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/intranet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/intranet/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;As part of the Edifecs rebrand in 2013, most internal and external systems received updates. Part 1 of this endeavor was to enhance many internal systems, such as the company&amp;rsquo;s SharePoint Intranet. The company felt that with the fact the company was rapidly growing, overall enhancements internally were needed to help employees and solidify the brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; SharePoint intranet and internal communication redesign project. Rebuilt to better employee communication and strengthen the company brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;problem:c397d4a98f94d377b2fb5b6ac7d31906&#34;&gt;Problem&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company was entering its 16th year, a lot of company growth was occurring. The market was changing rapidly due to national healthcare changes, and with many successes a lot of new employees were being hired. Going from some 200-ish to more than 500 worldwide in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many internal systems were not designed or provided well for the new volume of employees and projects. An overhaul of Edifecs&amp;rsquo; intranet and communications were needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-before-2013.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-before-2013-thumb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Intranet Before&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
    Original
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;solutions-and-goals:c397d4a98f94d377b2fb5b6ac7d31906&#34;&gt;Solutions and Goals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The internal solutions project is split into two areas, restructuring and design the SharePoint, and standardizing internal communications and branding. Especially providing a means to segment different locations, so that each office would not feel left out from headquarters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doing so would alleviate a lot of the stress and issues new employees and new teams would face. With less time being spent navigating administrative issues, more overall productivity could be had.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Internally, there is a strong push for company communication as well. This played a major role into internal design efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deliverables:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redesign Intranet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Restructure Intranet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email communication templates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;sharepoint-redesign-p1:c397d4a98f94d377b2fb5b6ac7d31906&#34;&gt;SharePoint Redesign p1&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/Process-flow.png&#34; alt=&#34;Homepage Project Track&#34; /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Homepage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the course of several quarters, the main landing page was redesigned and rebuilt. The focus for the homepage was derived after surveys and focus groups were preformed. The content focused on 3 parts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Latest news&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utlity items&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Calendar Events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research and Design&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several surveys were conducted within the company, asking employees likehart scale questions on different aspects of the company&amp;rsquo;s SharePoint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-survey.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-survey-thumb.png&#34; alt=&#34;Survey Results&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Focus groups were conducted as well. A group rating exercise along with a card sorting exercise was performed. The results coupled with the survey were very promising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some results:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tools - 20 points&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UI - 20 points&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social - 16 points&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Info - 9 Points&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Redesign&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several redesigns were worked through to accommodate the findings. The general designs and layout were refined and eventually approved by company leadership. Development started soon afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key homepage features:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company announcement news banner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A company news feed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Event Calendars&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quick links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Office specific links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From Mockup to Production
&lt;div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-mockup.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-mockup-thumb.png&#34; alt=&#34;Intranet Mockup&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
        Mockup - By Samuel Shen
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-final.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-final-thumb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Intranet Final&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
        Final Live Product
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;sharepoint-redesign-p2:c397d4a98f94d377b2fb5b6ac7d31906&#34;&gt;SharePoint Redesign p2&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Department Pages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After rolling out the new homepage, each department &lt;a href=&#34;https://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/library/cc262410.aspx&#34;&gt;site collection&lt;/a&gt; would receive redesigns for top level pages. Keeping each site collection at a high level consistent would allow any user to more easily navigate around. Before the redesign, each department site collection had its own design, layout, and information architecture. Company-wise, there was a general mandate/push that the information on site collections landing pages to be high level, so colleagues in other departments can more easily find information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The deeper the content pages, the less the page had to adhere to a strict design, as it became more likely it was just team specific at certain levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-sktech.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-sktech-thumb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Deparment site sketch&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
        Sketch
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-whiteboard.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-whiteboard-thumb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Deparment site whiteboard design&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
        Whiteboard
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-department-final.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/sharepoint-department-thumb.png&#34; alt=&#34;Deparment site final template&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
        Department Template
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;  

&lt;p&gt;In the end, it was decided that department site collection homepages should relect a similar style to that of the main homepage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Features:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;News Banner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tiles of major links to subpages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sidebar of links to resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;intenral-communication:c397d4a98f94d377b2fb5b6ac7d31906&#34;&gt;Intenral Communication&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Email Templates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Company wide emails are sent on a regular basis. Event announcements, customer wins, internal classes, etc&amp;hellip; For a long time in the company&amp;rsquo;s history, not standard email template was enforced. The lack of cohesion meant the information being delivered and written to employees was very inconsistent. By creating unified email templates for internal use, the company could accomplish a few important goals. Spread the new brand. Provide consistent and digestible information to employees. Each department and email template also gets its own micro-branding to help set each other apart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/email-final.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/email-thumb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sample email template&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
        Sample email template, dozens created in total
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;  

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blogs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To tie the internal redesign efforts together, each department got it&amp;rsquo;s own dedicated blog. The blogging system is tied directly to the email templates, so departments can create both items at once. Blog entries are saved to a SharePoint list, and that list is surfaced on the newly designed homepage. This doubles as an email archiving system as well.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#WhatIRun</title>
      <link>http://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/whatwerun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/whatwerun/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://whatwerun.com/&#34;&gt;WhatIRun&lt;/a&gt; asks employees, partners, customers, friends, and other women to join a conversation. To share what you run. Women are powerful. And most only see snippets or catch a glimpse into all what we manage and drive on a daily basis. The campaign partners with Ryka shoes, a women specific shoe brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-campaign-asking-women-what-they-run:083af8bfbbb136cccdf6a6f106aa9c4b&#34;&gt;A campaign asking women what they run&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/whatirun.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/whatirun-thumb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;What I Run Screenshot - Full screenshot 1 megabyte&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;goals:083af8bfbbb136cccdf6a6f106aa9c4b&#34;&gt;Goals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Create a site that allows women in industry to submit their profile information. Each profile is vetted and if approved, added to the site for display. The site would be featured at a HIMSS 2016 booth for convention goers to submit. Long term goals are to continue to market the cause to more people and grow the profile list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;strategy:083af8bfbbb136cccdf6a6f106aa9c4b&#34;&gt;Strategy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The general digital marketing strategy uses Twitter and direct messaging as a primary communication tool. Many profiles are expanded upon after submitting by reaching out to the submitter. Several individuals have even recorded video profiles for the campaign. All submitters are entered in to win a pair of Ryka athletic shoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;built-with:083af8bfbbb136cccdf6a6f106aa9c4b&#34;&gt;Built With&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wordpress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AWS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bamboo deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;achivements:083af8bfbbb136cccdf6a6f106aa9c4b&#34;&gt;Achivements&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since its launch, WhatIRun has had over 70 full submissions. This includes many tweets and social media mentions. Sentiment trackers show positive results. The campaign has been mentioned by &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/whatIrun/status/715659241600655364&#34;&gt;United Nations Women&lt;/a&gt;, then inundating the site with traffic.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mikes Amazing Cake Research</title>
      <link>http://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/cake/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;renowned-cake-maker-in-need-of-delicious-user-research:69a774f76c7f5f45c285aaa249ec6081&#34;&gt;Renowned cake maker in need of delicious user research&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mike’s Amazing Cakes increasing online presence is designed to showcase Pastry Chef Mike McCarey’s one-of-a-kind, customizable decorative cakes. His web presence is mostly primarily informative, but also has a commercial element in the sale of tutorial DVDs and other cake paraphernalia. In the world of digital marketing, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand who is interested in your services and why. The research done sheds light on possible featuring offerings and marketing tactics to be used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;problem:69a774f76c7f5f45c285aaa249ec6081&#34;&gt;Problem&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clients and information seekers online can differ from those seeking services through more &amp;lsquo;traditional&amp;rsquo; means. A problem that often affects businesses that made their start before the internet is knowing how to go about targeting the new digital audience. Although most of the tried and true market research techniques hold true today, the way to go about them has changed. Who is Mike&amp;rsquo;s online audience, and how can he better cater to them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;solution:69a774f76c7f5f45c285aaa249ec6081&#34;&gt;Solution&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provide and overall analysis into Mike&amp;rsquo;s Amazing Cakes website and digital presence, along with research into what can be doing to improve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deliverables&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Task Matrix &amp;amp; Personas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Usability test&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;results-and-findings:69a774f76c7f5f45c285aaa249ec6081&#34;&gt;Results and Findings&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;user-surveys:69a774f76c7f5f45c285aaa249ec6081&#34;&gt;User Surveys&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In three days, thirty-four users participated in the survey. Of those, 88% were first-time visitors. Surveying former and potential, along with comparing with existing customer data provided a lot of insight into users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The target audience breakdown based on surveys and analytics:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3% pastry student&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6% Event Planner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;11% Bride- or Groom-to-be&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;80% Members of the general public.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;personas-and-task-matrix:69a774f76c7f5f45c285aaa249ec6081&#34;&gt;Personas and Task Matrix&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;mdl-grid personas&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;cake mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34; style=&#34;background: url(&#39;/images/leena.jpg&#39;) bottom left 15% no-repeat&#34;&gt;&lt;h2 class=&#34;mdl-card__title-text&#34;&gt;Leena Singh (30)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&#34;My wedding must be perfect.&#34;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
    Grade School Teacher&lt;br&gt;
    Mountain View, CA&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;cake mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34; style=&#34;background: url(&#39;/images/jamie.jpg&#39;) bottom left 15% no-repeat&#34;&gt;&lt;h2 class=&#34;mdl-card__title-text&#34;&gt;Jamie Johnson (35)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&#34;Efficiency is everything.&#34;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
    Event Planner at Microsoft&lt;br&gt;
    Redmond, WA&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;cake mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34; style=&#34;background: url(&#39;/images/dman.jpg&#39;) bottom left 15% no-repeat&#34;&gt;
      &lt;h2 class=&#34;mdl-card__title-text&#34;&gt;Derek Atkinson (22)&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&#34;I’m a force to be reckoned with.&#34;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
    Caterer / Aspiring Cake Designer&lt;br&gt;
    New York, NY&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/task.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/task.png&#34; alt=&#34;Task Matrix&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;analytics:69a774f76c7f5f45c285aaa249ec6081&#34;&gt;Analytics&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With access to web analytics sources, the following demographics were determined:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% from US&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Average ages young 18-34&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Split for Male/Female&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MAC’s user has children&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sites that have more selection towards small sweets have more children&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education for MAC is high relative to the population.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prediction: income higher and stable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a job(s)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;User survey data suggests compliance with online analytics. The popularity of the site does not to correlate with user friendliness with the site. Each site controls a niche population within its region/state, hence popularity will remain low. Site usage remains similar even with some competitors offering more selection. Site usage is likely do to a brand trust relationship, rather than ease of use and availability. One problem with MAC is that 100% of users get to the site by searching for it, rather than typing it in directly. ~60% of users head to cakenology.com right after visiting MAC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;information-architecture:69a774f76c7f5f45c285aaa249ec6081&#34;&gt;Information Architecture&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The information architecture for many of the web properties could be realigned to better fit the targeted audiences. the following was created based on the analytics, personas, and a card sorting exercise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/IADiagramFinal-full.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/IADiagramFinal.png&#34; alt=&#34;Information Architecture of Mike&#39;s website&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hop on Hop off</title>
      <link>http://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/hopon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/hopon/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;frequent-business-travelers-can-easily-find-quick-city-tours:d4130ac0b1c9bb8ae9082b214ab75a2f&#34;&gt;Frequent business travelers can easily find quick city tours&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summer of 2012, a client approached me about designing an interesting service that was to cater to frequent travelers. I worked with the client to design and refine this concept service. I produced mobile designs for iOS, Android, and Windows Mobile based on the design standards at the time. The designs included interaction diagrams, spec docs, and an axure based interactive prototype.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/hop1.png&#34; alt=&#34;All three apps&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;problem:d4130ac0b1c9bb8ae9082b214ab75a2f&#34;&gt;Problem&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those that travel for business often only have a few hours free in the location they travel to. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m in Venice and my meetings over. Why waste time cooped up in your hotel?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;solution:d4130ac0b1c9bb8ae9082b214ab75a2f&#34;&gt;Solution&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most major cities have a &lt;strong&gt;Hop On Hop Off&lt;/strong&gt; style tour bus system, which is easily accessible to most tourist. Design a service that provides a list and routes of current tour busses. Partner with local businesses to provide different incentives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;app-flow-and-screenshots:d4130ac0b1c9bb8ae9082b214ab75a2f&#34;&gt;App Flow and Screenshots&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/App-flow-android-full.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/App-flow-android.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;App Flow&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/hop-wp-small.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Windows Phone example&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/hop-and-small.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Android Holo example&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collection of other works</title>
      <link>http://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://christopher-nguyen.com/portfolio/other/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-simple-list-of-some-other-works:ce5140e349b63a61e819dec03e0e3cef&#34;&gt;A simple list of some other works.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;indianight.party&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/india-night.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
    India Night Event
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;//round.glass&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/round-glass.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
    Round Glass Website
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/fb-banner.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/fb-banner-thumb.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
    Facebook Page Banners
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/fb-ads.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/fb-ads-thumb.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
    Facebook Ads
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/fedd.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/fedd-thumb.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
    FEED Charity Drive
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card mdl-shadow--2dp thumb-card&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__title mdl-card--expand&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/shipiyi.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://christopher-nguyen.com/images/shipiyi-thumb.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;mdl-card__supporting-text&#34;&gt;
    Shipyizi Business Card
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>